megabuy.com.au 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | MegaBuy Computer Parts

Browsers Online: 355

Members Online: 7

|  |  |   
---  
  
At MegaBuy your privacy is our priority. We are committed to protecting your privacy at all times and in all situations. The information we collect about you when you become a member is used to process your orders and to provide a more personalised experience on our website. Our website uses 128 bit encryption in areas of the website where personal information is collected or displayed to increase the security of any information transmitted between your computer and our website. However, please note that we cannot guarantee complete security of all stored information, although, we do everything in our power to ensure that all information is secure.

**How Do We Use the Information We Collect?**  
When you become a MegaBuy member, we ask you to fill out a form that requests your name, address and e-mail address. MegaBuy Pty. Ltd. may share this data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis.

Your name, email and address information is used solely to process orders unless you give prior consent for this information to be used for other purposes. Without your consent, this information will NEVER be sold, given, rented or traded to others for purposes other than order fulfillment.

**Refer-A-Friend**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. MegaBuy Pty. Ltd. does not store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

**Our Use of Log Files**  
When you visit our website we automatically log your IP address, your browser type and your access times. We utilize this information to conduct website performance evaluations, to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click data (the pages our users visit on our website). This data helps us determine what content our members find most appealing so that we can improve your use of our website.

**Site Security**  
All MegaBuy employees take your personal information very seriously. All employees are required learn and comply with our security policies. Access to personal information of website members is limited to our employees.

**Correcting/Updating Your Personal Information**  
After becoming a MegaBuy member you may correct/update your personal information by clicking on the 'My Account' link at the top of any page, entering your E-Mail Address and Password when prompted and clicking the View or change my account information link. The changes you make will be reflected in our databases instantly. If you wish to deactivate your account, you should contact us via the 'Contact Us' page and request for your account to be deactivated.

**Links To Other Sites**  
This website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you may be leaving the MegaBuy website and entering another website. These websites may independently collect or request information about you and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these websites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

**Communication**  
From time to time we may send out email messages alerting you that products are available, to remind you about providing feedback or for promotional offers. In addition, you will receive communication from us 1) if you contact us for a particular reason, 2) to receive your orders, or 3) we need to contact you for administrative purposes such as winning a contest. If you choose to receive our Newsletters, they may contain promotional materials from MegaBuy and our partners.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.

**Supplementation**  
We may correct or supplement your address information with standardised postal representation in order to ensure that your orders are delivered.

**Contests**  
Periodically, contests may be run on our website. Sometimes contests are sponsored by our suppliers and/or partners. To enter these contests you may need to enter your Name, E-Mail Address and/or Password. At the time of entry, you may decide if you wish to have your name posted on our website if you are the winner. Winners' names are NEVER shared with our customers without their consent.

**Our Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer's hard drive which identify you when you enter. We may use session cookies to provide a seamless experience on the website and to combine with our log files so that we can understand our website traffic and analyze website usage information in aggregate form.

**Your Feedback is Always Welcome**  
We welcome your comments and questions about our privacy policy - or anything else you might want to discuss. Please contact us by going to our Contact Us page.

You can also reach us via email at admin@MegaBuy.com.au  
  
|  |   
---  

  * G.Denton - 16 Jan 12

Hi just wanted to say, I have no idea why you guys have such bad reviews. I received my products within 3 days and the Macbook Pro was a 2 week wait but I expected that nothing would ship until after the huge sale! Awesome prices on everything. Couldn't have been happier.

Thanks again to everyone I was in contact with along the way!

  * Roger B - 24 Feb 12

Received in good order yesterday. Thankyou and congratulations to all your staff for TOP service. Will certainly recommend and use your services again. 

  * Geoffrey S - 29 Jun 12

Hello, Just to let you know that my computer monitor arrived yesterday. I am very pleased with it and I compliment your company's fast delivery time and professional service. I may purchase another monitor in the future for a spare as I desire a monitor with inbult speakers and most of the monitors available these days don't appear to have this feature. As for the BenQ monitor, I would recommend it highly for future purchasers.  

  * Geoffrey S - 29 Jun 12

Hello, Just to let you know that my computer monitor arrived yesterday. I am very pleased with it and I compliment your company's fast delivery time and professional service. I may purchase another monitor in the future for a spare as I desire a monitor with inbult speakers and most of the monitors available these days don't appear to have this feature. As for the BenQ monitor, I would recommend it highly for future purchasers.  

  * Warrick T - 25 Oct 12

For your information; I have just confirmed that my item has just been recieved and I appreciate it very much.To you and all your your team; Keep up the good work  

  * Christine N - 02 Nov 12

Just received my order today and just wanted to say THANKS! Super impressed at the speed of handling and delivery - exceeded expectations by a long shot. Thank you too for keeping me so thoroughly updated on the progress of my order. Really appreciate it - keep up the great work!  

  * Craig L - 21 Nov 12

I would like to thank the MegaBuy team. I ordered my item on Monday of this week and it arrived safely today. This is my first ever on-line purchase and it has been a great experience with prompt responses from the customer service team.Thank you again  

  * W. Spratley - 03 Jan 13

I would like to take the time to write to you in regards to my order. I realise the holiday season is difficult to deal with and you have shown me a prompt service given the circumstances   
Thank you. I look forward to doing business with you in the near future.  

  * T. Smith - 09 Jan 13

To the MegaBuy Team.

Just letting you know that my item arrived today and must say that's the fastest order I have ever received.   
your communication was also second to none and will definitely buy again from you.  
many thanks to you all.

  * Dan N - 10 Jan 13

Thank you very much. I am very impressed with the quality and professionalism of your service and will recommend this business to others. Thankyou 

  * M.Gardner - 15 Jan 13

Hi - I received my order in regional NT two days after ordering online! Perfect product, works very well and straight away (Order 193286). 

Many thanks again, especially for the super quick processing and delivery, you have one happy customer and congratulations to all your team on a job well done!

Cheers

  * C. Gilroy - 25 Jan 13

Hi MegaBuy, Thank you for your very prompt service. I received the disc today. Well done.

Kind regards,

Chris

  * C. Roebuck - 25 Jan 13

I am very impressed with MegaBuy.   
Communication was professional, I received my well packed items safely, delivered by excellent couriers, promptly.   
Would not hesitate to recommend your site, for proficient and efficient service! 

Thank you.

  * R. Sullivan - 31 Jan 13

Just wanted to say thank you the rep I spoke to yesterday said it would show up today and it did.  
Thanks  

  * S. Blair - 07 Feb 13

Easy website to use; good forms with follow up email with order. Competitive pricing too. 

  * John V - 08 Feb 13

Got it thank you. You provide excellent customer service - top web page, good payment system, good communications. Well done. 

  * M. Alexander - 28 Feb 13

Got it! Love it! Will definitely be telling everyone about your fantastic company.  
Job extremely well done Megabuy, thank you all so very much.  

  * Brad.H - 01 May 13

Thanks Megabuy - great service!!! Ordered the item on Wednesday, it was here in Darwin on Monday, with a public holiday in between.  
Excellent prompt service, good price and realistic shipping charges (unlike others).

Well done.

I will deal with you again.

Regards  
Brad

  * Lachlan.B - 01 May 13

Hi, I ordered my GS105AU switch from you guys over the phone. I just want to say how good the service was and how nice the customer service Representative was to me, even though i did not have the correct information I had at the time. So yeah, awesome service thank you Jack G! Sincerely, a returning Megabuy customer  

  * Peter M - 02 May 13

Hi, I just received my order and I am mightily impressed. The whole process from the minute I clicked onto your website for the first time yesterday right through to receipt of my item today was brilliant. I was especially impressed with your order confirmation process to ensure that my order placed using a gmail email address was in fact placed by me. I still cannot believe that I received delivery of my item in about 24hrs, though I dont know if I can hold you to that if I have to place another order :-) I will definitely recommend Megabuy to others and will use your services again in the future should the need arise. Again thank you so much for a brilliant purchase experience.  

  * Mite .T. - 08 May 13

Thanks for the ultra quick delivery guys. This is my first purchase from you guys, but definately wont be the last.. Very happy customer! 

  * U. Grebe - 22 May 13

Just letting you know was very impressed with service received. Was delivered in under 24 hrs well done. Thanks 

  * A. Karanwal - 31 May 13

Hi, Received it this arvo! Appreciate the super-quick delivery!!   
Shopped with you for the first time, inspite of the negative reviews on OzBargain, but I have no complains. Have passed on the good word and posted a link on my FB page too!  
Thanks,  

  * A.Walsh - 03 Jun 13

A BIG COMPLIMENT!!!

Late last Friday morning I ordered some software from you guys. I am in Canberra. At 11.45 this morning - Monday - it was delivered!  
Let me sum up:

1\. Best price I could find on what I was buying.  
2\. Only marginally less quick than if I had taken the trouble to go to a specialist store to buy it personally, and DEFINITELY faster than if I had bought from the developer on line.  
3\. A bonus of a local delveryman who, from experience, knew the vagaries of accessing where I live and made it simple (OK - you guys couldn't have organised that, but it was a nice and welcome extra)!

Simply put - this is my first Megabuy purchase. It is unlikely to be my last!  
Many thanks.

  * Lorraine H - 12 Aug 13

Thank you very much for your extremely efficient system. We received out order in record time. As we live in WA we are use to our orders taking a day or two longer than is written on websites but we couldnt fault your delivery time. It was super fast.  
We have ordered another product from another site who told us it would take 2-3 days and we actually ordered this before ordering from Mega Buy. We are still waiting! It is now 7 days and counting. We will be back to Mega Buy and will recommend your site without hesitation to others. Thank you.  

  * Dave - 29 Aug 13

Just wanted to give you the thumbs up for the product I recently bought. I bought a graphics card and it was delivered under 2 working days later! Pricing was competitive and service great! Will definitely be using MegaBuy again! 

  * Howard - 02 Sep 13

I am very careful buyer, especially when buying items online, I do a lot of research about the background of the sellers, and read reviews to get a good idea about the genuinity of the seller. I have bought many items from sellers, from around the world. So i talk with a conviction. I recently bought an item from "MegaBuy", and I can say for certain that this seller is one of the most genuine online sellers who handles sales in a very professional way.To anyone who is careful and not sure who to trust when buying from online, I can tell you with a conviction, buy from this seller "MegaBuy" , without having any fear of being 'ripped off'. The products are "Genuine", the packaging of the item are excellent, and everything is done in a professional way. "MegaBuy", Good on you , and keep doing the excellent good work. All the best to all at MegaBuy. You are all Awesome. 

  * Peter Wishart - 05 Sep 13

"Wow" Great Service I received my order this morning.  
I will look forward to my next megabuy purchase. 

  * Anthony Wardley - 11 Dec 13

Hi, I contacted you earlier, just letting you know Applecare has come through fine this morning. Thank you so much I really appreciate it. Loved the fast shipping and the pricing. Well done. 

  * George Oltvolgyi - 06 May 14

Thank you very much for your prompt, courteous and professional service.  
My Xtremkey turned up yesterday safely packaged and well within the anticipated timeframe.  
Will definitely come back. 

  * G.Denton - 16 Jan 12

Hi just wanted to say, I have no idea why you guys have such bad reviews. I received my products within 3 days and the Macbook Pro was a 2 week wait but I expected that nothing would ship until after the huge sale! Awesome prices on everything. Couldn't have been happier.

Thanks again to everyone I was in contact with along the way!
